simplyscripts.com 2002-04-05

# Screenwriting Contests

## Copyright

No graphics, pages, html, banners, etc., found on this site may be reproduced, posted, or sold without the consent of Simply Scripts. 

## Disclaimer

Simply Scripts does not guarantee the accuracy of the information presented on this page. Simply Scripts claims no relation to any of the sites or scripts listed on this page outside of simplyscripts.com or simplyscripts.home.att.net. Simplyscripts does not control or endorse the content of third party Web Sites. All information is provided "as is" and a link to a site does not, in any way, represent or imply an approval of or a determination of the quality of that product or service. The links outside of simplyscripts.com or simplyscripts.home.att.net are maintained by their respective organizations or webmasters, and they are solely responsible for their content. Users agree to hold Simply Scripts harmless for any and all damages arising out of use of this service and links from this service and the services related thereto. Film related properties mentioned herein are © to their respective owners. 

## Privacy Statement

Simply Scripts respects your privacy. All information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to Simply Scripts will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to.  
Disclosure of information to third parties: Simply Scripts does not and will not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms, email lists, or emails sent to the webmaster asking questions or requesting information. 

**Browser information collected on Simply Scripts:** Simply Scripts does not collect click steam data. However, hitbox.com, of which Simply Scripts is an affiliate collects, click stream data such as web surfer's IP address, web pages on Simplyscripts.com which have been viewed by a web surfer, date and time, domain type, and originating url. Simply Scripts does not collect personally identifiable information unless it is given to Simply Script through an email. That information is and will not be disclosed to a third party.

**Use of Cookies:** Simply Scripts does not use cookies. HOWEVER, affiliates of Simply Scripts may use cookies. Listed below are all of Simply Scripts affiliates with links to their Privacy Policies.

**Privacy of emails and email lists:** Any and all emails sent to Simply Scripts are held in the strictest confidence. The contents of the emails will not be shared, sold, reused, rented, loaned or otherwise disclosed to a third party without the consent of the sender. The Simply Script email list will not be shared, sold, reused, rented, loaded or otherwise disclosed to a third party without the consent of the sender. In addition, Simply Scripts will insure that our list server software is configured such that it will not divulge the email addresses of list subscribers to anyone, including other subscribers. 

**EXCEPTION TO EMAIL PRIVACY POLICY:** When you submit an original script to either be hosted on the simplyscripts.com domain OR submit a link to a script you have written, you are giving me permission to post your work or link to your work on the site. In addition, you are giving me permission to post your email address on simplyscripts.com. 

If you have any questions regarding Simply Scripts' privacy policy, please notify the webmaster.

Simply Scripts Affiliates and their Privacy Policies:  
[Hitbox.com](http://hitbox.com/) \- [privacy policy](http://www.websidestory.com/privacy/)  
[All Posters.com](http://affiliates.allposters.com/link/redirect.asp?aid=4658) \- [privacy policy](http://allposters.com/aboutus/privacy.asp)  
[Amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect-home/simplyscripts) \- [privacy policy](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/browse/-/468496/simplyscripts/)  
[GoTo.com](http://service.bfast.com/bfast/click?bfmid=253985&bfsiteid=10377817&bfpage=homelink4) \- [privacy policy](http://goto.com/d/about/company/privacypolicy.jhtml)  
[Windward Studios](http://store.windward.net/screenwriterstudio.jsp?sourceID=14) \- no privacy policy  
[Commission Junction](http://www.qksrv.net/click-524565-13337) \- [privacy policy](http://cj.com/privacy.asp)
